chris gardner
كريس غاردنر
how are you
كيف حالك
good morning
صباح الخير
chris gardner
كريس غاردنر
chris carter good to see you again
كريس كارتر، سعيد لرؤيتك مرة أخرى
chris gardner pleasure
كريس غاردنر، من دواعي سروري
i&#39;ve been sitting out there for the last
لقد كنت جالسًا هناك لمدة
half hour trying to come up with a story
نصف ساعة أحاول أن أخرج بقصة
that would explain my being here
تفسر وجودي هنا
dressed
مرتديًا
like this
مثل هذا
and and i wanted to come up with a story
وأردت أن أخرج بقصة
that would demonstrate qualities that
تظهر الصفات التي
i&#39;m sure you all admire here like like
أنا متأكد أنكم جميعًا تعجبون بها هنا مثل
earnestness
الجدية
or diligence and
أو الاجتهاد و
team playing to something and i couldn&#39;t
العمل الجماعي على شيء ولم أستطع
think
التفكير
of anything
في أي شيء
so the truth is
لذا الحقيقة هي
i was arrested for failure to pay
أنني اعتُقلت بسبب عدم دفع
parking tickets parking figures
تذاكر وقوف السيارات
and i ran all the way here from the polk
وعدت هنا من محطة
station the police station
الشرطة
what were you doing before you were
ماذا كنت تفعل قبل أن تُعتقل؟
arrested i was uh
كنت أuh
painting my apartment
أقوم بطلاء شقتي
did you dry now
هل جف الآن؟
i hope so
آمل ذلك
jay says you&#39;re pretty determined oh
يقول جاي أنك مصمم جدًا، أوه
he&#39;s been waiting outside the front of
لقد كان ينتظر خارج المدخل
the building with some 40-pound gizmo
المبنى مع جهاز يزن حوالي 40 رطلاً
for over a month
لأكثر من شهر
he said you&#39;re smart
قال إنك ذكي
i&#39;d like to think so
أود أن أعتقد ذلك
and you want to learn this business yes
وأنت تريد أن تتعلم هذا العمل، نعم
sir i want to learn this business have
سيدي، أريد أن أتعلم هذا العمل
you already started learning on your own
هل بدأت بالفعل في التعلم بمفردك؟
absolutely
بالتأكيد
jay yes sir
جاي، نعم سيدي
how many times have you seen chris
كم مرة رأيت كريس؟
no i don&#39;t know
لا، لا أعرف
one too many apparently
مرة واحدة أكثر من اللازم على ما يبدو
has he ever dressed like this no
هل ارتدى هكذا من قبل؟ لا
no
لا
jacket and ty
سترة وربطة عنق
first in your class
الأول في صفك
in school
في المدرسة
high school yes sir
مدرسة ثانوية نعم سيدي
how many in the class
كم عدد الطلاب في الصف
uh 12. it was a small town
أuh 12. كانت بلدة صغيرة
i&#39;ll say but i was also first in my
سأقول لكنني كنت أيضًا الأول في
radar class in in the navy and that was
فصل الرادار في البحرية وكان ذلك
a class of 20.
فصل من 20.
can i say something
هل يمكنني قول شيء
um
أم
i&#39;m the type of person
أنا من نوع الأشخاص
if you ask me a question and i don&#39;t
إذا سألتني سؤالًا ولم أ
know the answer
أعرف الإجابة
i&#39;m gonna tell you that i don&#39;t know
سأخبرك أنني لا أعرف
but i bet you what
لكن أراهن أنك ماذا
i know how to find the answer and i will
أعرف كيف أجد الإجابة وسأ
find the answer
أجد الإجابة
is that fair enough
هل هذا عادل بما فيه الكفاية
chris
كريس
what would you say
ماذا ستقول
if a guy walked in for an interview
إذا دخل رجل لمقابلة
without a shirt
بدون قميص
on and i hired him what would you say
وعينته ماذا ستقول
he must have had on some really nice
لابد أنه كان يرتدي بعض
pants
السراويل الجميلة
[Laughter]
[ضحك]
chris
كريس
i don&#39;t know how you did it dressed as a
لا أعرف كيف فعلت ذلك مرتديًا زي
garbage man but you really pulled it off
عامل القمامة لكنك فعلتها حقًا
in there thank you very much mr twistle
هناك شكرًا جزيلاً لك السيد تويستل
hey now you can call me jay all right
مرحبًا الآن يمكنك مناداتي جاي حسنًا
we&#39;ll talk to you soon all right so i&#39;ll
سنتحدث قريبًا حسنًا سأ
let you know jay
أخبرك جاي
you&#39;ll let me know jay
ستخبرني جاي
what do you mean yeah i&#39;ll give you a
ماذا تعني نعم سأعطيك
call tomorrow sometime what what are you
اتصالًا غدًا في وقت ما ماذا ماذا
talking you hounded me for this you
تتحدث لقد كنت تضغط علي من أجل هذا
stood here listen there&#39;s no salary no i
وقفت هنا استمع لا يوجد راتب لا أنا
was not aware of that my circumstances
لم أكن على علم بذلك ظروفي
have changed some and
تغيرت بعض الشيء و
i need to be certain that i&#39;ll be able
أحتاج أن أكون متأكدًا من أنني سأكون قادرًا
to
على
okay
حسنًا
tonight
الليلة
i swear i will fill your spot i promise
أقسم سأملأ مكانك أعدك
you i&#39;ll look like if you back out you
سأبدو كما لو أنك تراجعت أنت
know what i&#39;ll look like to the partners
تعرف كيف سأبدو للشركاء
yes and ass
نعم و
an ass
أحمق
all the way
حتى النهاية
you are a piece of work
أنت قطعة من العمل
tonight
الليلة
you
أنت